const quizzes = [
  {
    id: 1,
    name: "Much or Many",
    questions: [
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "___ Copy-books",
        options: ["Much", "Many"],
        correctAnswer: "Many"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "___ Milk",
        options: ["Much", "Many"],
        correctAnswer: "Much"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "___ Days",
        options: ["Much", "Many"],
        correctAnswer: "Many"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "___ Chalk",
        options: ["Much", "Many"],
        correctAnswer: "Many"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "___ Pictures",
        options: ["Much", "Many"],
        correctAnswer: "Many"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "___ Rooms",
        options: ["Much", "Many"],
        correctAnswer: "Many"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "___ Work",
        options: ["Much", "Many"],
        correctAnswer: "Much"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "___ Money",
        options: ["Much", "Many"],
        correctAnswer: "Much"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "___ Cars",
        options: ["Much", "Many"],
        correctAnswer: "Many"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "___ teachers",
        options: ["Much", "Many"],
        correctAnswer: "Many"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "___ students",
        options: ["Much", "Many"],
        correctAnswer: "Many"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "___ information",
        options: ["Much", "Many"],
        correctAnswer: "Much"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "___ dogs",
        options: ["Much", "Many"],
        correctAnswer: "Many"
      },      
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "___ busses",
        options: ["Much", "Many"],
        correctAnswer: "Many"
      },

    ]
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    name: "Формы слога",
    questions: [
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "Pick",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "mole",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "ship",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "me",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "sum",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "be",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "lie",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "take",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "help",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "fly",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "date",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "cut",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "I",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "list",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "mule",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "check",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "site",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "hot",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "pen",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "student",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "black",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "tube",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "but",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "symbol",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "men",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "ten",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "five",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "lamp",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "life",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "flag",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "wine",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "lit",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "pot",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "we",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "vale",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "tune",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "map",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "lot",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "did",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "lat",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "carry",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "hit",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "due",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "my",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "fat",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Closed"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "cry",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      },
      {
        type: "multiple-choice",
        questionText: "fame",
        options: ["Open", "Closed"],
        correctAnswer: "Open"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 3,
  name: "Третья форма слога",
  questions: [
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "Name",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Open"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "form",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "her",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Silent"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "sort",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "dress",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "see",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Open"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "dark",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "hand",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Silent"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "black",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "cake",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Open"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "sock",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "green",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Open"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "place",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Open"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "long",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "men",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "farmer",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "home",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Open"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "we",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Open"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "nose",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Open"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "morning",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "arm",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "cap",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "then",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "car",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "butter",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "student",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "like",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Open"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "skirt",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Silent"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "lip",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "drink",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "put",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "turn",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Silent"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "first",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Silent"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "blue",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "fine",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Open"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "number",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "tie",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Open"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "sum",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "milk",
      options: ["Open", "Closed", "Silent"],
      correctAnswer: "Closed"
    }
  ]
},
{
  id: 4,
  name: "Суфикс -IAN",
  questions: [
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "Russia + -ian = _____",
      correctAnswer: "Russian"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "Brazil + -ian = _____",
      correctAnswer: "Brazilian"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "Norway + -ian = _____",
      correctAnswer: "Norwegian"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "Slovakia + -ian = _____",
      correctAnswer: "Slovakian"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "Canada + -ian = _____",
      correctAnswer: "Canadian"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "Egypt + -ian = _____",
      correctAnswer: "Egyptian"
    }
  ]
},
{
  id: 5,
  name: "Артикуль a/an",
  questions: [
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "rubber",
      options: ["a", "an"],
      correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "apple",
      options: ["a", "an"],
      correctAnswer: "an"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "boy",
      options: ["a", "an"],
      correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "inkjet printer",
      options: ["a", "an"],
      correctAnswer: "an"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "book",
      options: ["a", "an"],
      correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "rule",
      options: ["a", "an"],
      correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "orange",
      options: ["a", "an"],
      correctAnswer: "an"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "ant",
      options: ["a", "an"],
      correctAnswer: "an"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "engineer",
      options: ["a", "an"],
      correctAnswer: "an"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "girl",
      options: ["a", "an"],
      correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "office",
      options: ["a", "an"],
      correctAnswer: "an"
    }
  ]
},
{
  id: 101,
  name: "Времена года",
  questions: [
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "Winter - _____",
      correctAnswer: "зима"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "December - _____",
      correctAnswer: "декабрь"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "January - _____",
      correctAnswer: "январь"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "February - _____",
      correctAnswer: "февраль"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "Spring - _____",
      correctAnswer: "весна"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "March - _____",
      correctAnswer: "март"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "April - _____",
      correctAnswer: "апрель"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "May - _____",
      correctAnswer: "май"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "Summer - _____",
      correctAnswer: "лето"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "June - _____",
      correctAnswer: "июнь"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "July - _____",
      correctAnswer: "июль"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "August - _____",
      correctAnswer: "август"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "Autumn - _____",
      correctAnswer: "осень"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "September - _____",
      correctAnswer: "сентябрь"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "October - _____",
      correctAnswer: "октябрь"
    },
    {
      type: "fill-in-the-blank",
      questionText: "November - _____",
      correctAnswer: "ноябрь"
    }
  ]
},
{
  id: 102,
  name: "This is / These are",
  questions: [
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "1. _____ a manager.",
      options: ["This is", "These are"],
      correctAnswer: "This is"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "2. ____ workers.",
      options: ["This is", "These are"],
      correctAnswer: "These are"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "3. ____ a clerk.",
      options: ["This is", "These are"],
      correctAnswer: "This is"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "4. ____ a mechanic.",
      options: ["This is", "These are"],
      correctAnswer: "This is"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "5. ____ drivers.",
      options: ["This is", "These are"],
      correctAnswer: "These are"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "6. ____ a programmer.",
      options: ["This is", "These are"],
      correctAnswer: "This is"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "7. ____ doctors.",
      options: ["This is", "These are"],
      correctAnswer: "These are"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "8. ____ a teacher.",
      options: ["This is", "These are"],
      correctAnswer: "This is"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "9. ____ a designer.",
      options: ["This is", "These are"],
      correctAnswer: "This is"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "10. ____ system administrators.",
      options: ["This is", "These are"],
      correctAnswer: "These are"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "11. _____ men.",
      options: ["This is", "These are"],
      correctAnswer: "These are"
    },
    {
      type: "multiple-choice",
      questionText: "12. _____ feet.",
      options: ["This is", "These are"],
      correctAnswer: "These are"
    }
  ]
}
];

export default quizzes;